admin-talk.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Admin Talk Forums

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analyzed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognized by our web servers.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Information Collection**  
Admin Talk Forums is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or share this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Be aware that by choosing to show your email address, Admin Talk Forums can not be held responsible for any unsolicited emails that might be a result of choosing to show your email address. To make sure your email address is kept private we use an email form and private messaging system so that you can contact other forum members.

If you receive unsolicited email from anyone using the sites email form or private messaging system use our [Contact Forum](http://admin-talk.com/forums/contact-the-staff.222/ "External link") to report the user who sent he unsolicited email or private message.

 **Cookies**  
Admin Talk Forums uses cookies to keep track of our members and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Other information stored in the cookie is last time you logged in, your username, and your preferred topic view. These cookies are stored in your browser and can be cleared by logging out. It is advised to clear your cookie after each visit to ensure that your information is safe if more than one person has access to the computer you use.

 **Advertisements**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information.  

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "External link").

For further information about the DoubleClick DART cookie visit this link:  

 **Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are displayed to administrators and moderators and may be used to deny access to abusive members.

**Links**  
Some of the posts may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we at Admin Talk Forums are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Admin Talk Forums.

 **Security**  
Admin Talk Forums takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Vital information, such as your password, is stored encrypted in our database to ensure your account is secure.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send us an email by using our Contact Form to inquire about our security practices.

 **Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site you can:

Or you can write us at:

Admin Talk Forums  
c/o Robert Schwarz, Sr.  
1417 Brentwood PL  
Joliet, IL U.S.A 60435

Published:
    Aug 3, 2013
Page views:
    1,779
